teamworkpm.net 2017-06-02

# Teamwork.com - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of great importance to us. This Privacy Policy exists to tell you what kind of information we may gather while you visit our website and how we may use such information.

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about individuals with two exceptions: when such information is voluntarily submitted by the visitor through forms, and some incidental statistics of site usage which are collected automatically.

###  Personal Information You Choose to Provide

In order to enable visitors of our website to see certain pages, when specifically requested by them, we require some contact information, (such as name, and e-mail address). The information collected shall be used for the purposes specified when it was collected, to respond to visitor’s inquiries, and fulfill e-mail messaging programs to notify visitors about new content or services on our website.

Any information given to us shall be stored and managed the greatest care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. We will not sell, rent, or exchange such personally identifiable information to any other organization or entity. Notwithstanding the above, we may indeed disclose personal information if required to do so by subpoenas, court orders or legal process or when such disclosure is made for establishment or exercise of legal rights or in defending against legal claim, or as otherwise required by law.

If you decide you no longer wish to receive postal mailings and/or e-mails from us, please let us know by sending an e-mail or writing to us and telling us you no longer wish to receive postal mail and/or e-mail. Please provide us with your exact name, postal address, and/or e-mail address. We will make sure your name is removed from our mailing list.

###  Information Automatically Collected and Stored

In common with many websites, we also measure the performance of our website in order to improve and customize it in favor of our visitors. During your visit, we may automatically collect and temporarily store certain usage information about visits to our websites. This information may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring/ existing pages and URLs, domain names, pages viewed and the date and time of your request and other such information that uniquely identify your browser. Such information is used for system administration and for producing usage statistics. We may entrust third parties with the described performance measurement. Such third parties will be required to use appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Our website may deposit certain bits of information called "cookies" in a visitor’s computer. Generally, a cookie assigns a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Cookies can tell us how and when pages in a website are visited and by how many people. This technology does not collect an individual visitor’s identifying information; rather, this information is also in an aggregate form. The purpose of this technology and the information it provides is again to help us improve our website. Most web browsers allow the user to deny or accept the cookie feature. However, please note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features (e.g. customized delivery of information) available on our website. Further information about cookies can be found at http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx

###  Linked Sites

Links on this Site to websites are provided as a convenience to you. Such linked sites are outside our control and responsibility and are not covered by this policy. If you use any such linked sites, you should consult the privacy policies posted on those websites.  

###  User's Data

Upon a user's request, we shall remove all the user's data from the website. All removed user's data shall be kept for three additional months (offline) before deletion.  

###  Security

Although we take necessary measures in order to provide a secure website we can not fully control and therefore can not be liable for all interruptions, intrusions, errors, loss of data or any other interferences with the use of this website caused by a breach of security.  

###  Limitation of Liability

Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall we be liable for any special or consequential damages that results from the use of, or the inability to use, the website and the materials in it.  
Without derogating the aforementioned, in no event shall our total liability exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing the site.  

###  Contact information

For any question or to request modification or deletion of your personal information, please e-mail info@teamwork.com  

###  Changes and Updates to this Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will provide notification of the change on our website. The Privacy Policy does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.
